<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-07-08T19:08:49+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Hecrenews</title><entry><title type="html">Alpacas or Llamas</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2021/07/08/alpaca-or-llamas.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Alpacas or Llamas" /><published>2021-07-08T23:03:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-07-08T23:03:00+00:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2021/07/08/alpaca-or-llamas</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2021/07/08/alpaca-or-llamas.html">&lt;p&gt;It is time to settle the debate, alpacas, or llamas?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First off, what are these two?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is an alpaca
&lt;img src=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/assets/images/alpaca.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is a llama
&lt;img src=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/assets/images/llama.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both can be found in Peru, and are part of Camelidae, the camel family. It may not jump out to you immediately, but camels are part of camelidae as well, making camels
the alpaca/llama of Africa and Asia. There are four lamoid species: alpaca, llama, vicuña, and guanaco. All four can mix and combine to create offspring, it’s like
a mix and match burrito deal! Here we are not going to set aside their differences, but instead bring up their differences to determine who is the best lamoid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;size&quot;&gt;Size&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Llamas are bigger, and that’s pretty much the end of the story there. Not only are llamas bigger than alpacas, but llamas are the biggest lamoid of the bunch,
deserving bonus points! Looks like llamas got a lead in this one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;face&quot;&gt;Face&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alpacas have smaller, more blunt faces with short ears. Llamas have more elongated faces with ears the size of bananas! Judging someone by their face isn’t really
fair, so I’m told in a situation like this you guys can discuss in the comments below to see which lamoid has the better face.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;hair&quot;&gt;Hair&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alpacas have shaggy, big, fluffy hair that can be used for fleece, and they come in many fun colours such as white, yellow, brown, and black. Llama wool is simply
considered inferior. Looks like alpacas are combing back into the game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;behavior&quot;&gt;Behavior&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Llamas can carry a lot. 45 to 60kg for up to 30km every day. That is brute strength that your poor Pablo here can never manage to pull off. However, at there is a
cost. Llamas like to complain a lot. I’ve seen it live in action. If you overwork them, or treat them badly, llamas will spit, kick, lie down, and/or refuse to
move. However, this is only when you push them to their limits, since otherwise they are pretty tame. Alpacas are more timid and like to stay with their herd.
However, here is the real kicker. Llamas can be used as guard animals for livestock like alpacas and sheep. Llamas are guarding the alpacas! I think this alone
proves their dominance, even more so the fact that alpaca need to be guarded like sheep. Can you believe it, alpaca are like sheep! I think the debate here is over,
llamas are a clear winner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, new discoveries happen all the time. I wouldn’t be surprised if a researcher found a groundbreaking fact that makes llamas insignificant to alpacas, but for
now, llamas are clearly the GOAT. You can count on your friendly neighborhood Pablo to keep you updated on the things hip and happening in Peru. You may have noticed
I didn’t call in SAR, our resarch team here at the Hecrenews, well don’t worry, because when in Peru, you just have pure knowledge of these things, it is essential
to the way of life. Anywho, did you agree or disagree?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>pablo</name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><category term="News" /><category term="Politics" /><summary type="html">It is time to settle the debate, alpacas, or llamas?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Another Victory for Hecrenews: Rival Newsite Loses by Default</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2021/07/06/rival-newsite-loses-by-default.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Another Victory for Hecrenews: Rival Newsite Loses by Default" /><published>2021-07-06T01:41:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-07-06T01:41:00+00:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2021/07/06/rival-newsite-loses-by-default</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2021/07/06/rival-newsite-loses-by-default.html">&lt;p&gt;Hello hello, it’s ya boi Mister Mjir popping in for another one. Yes it’s been a while but things at out Hecrenews branch have been quite busy, so I didn’t get time
to really dig down deep into a story and produce an article about it. Anyways, here’s the scoop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may remember we were dealing with a rival newsite problem. Unlike many other fake news site and news companies that spam ads and clickbait articles, this newsite
was legit, and of the same caliber. Welp, no point in beating around the bush, let’s cut to the chase. &lt;a href=&quot;https://melnewzers.blogspot.com/&quot;&gt;MELnewzers&lt;/a&gt; is the rival
newsite we were dealing with. We already had spies infiltrating their ranks- I think Wopps knows more if he wants to do a follow up article -and we were keeping them
at bay. MEL stands for Motivation, Energy, and Life, or something along those lines, I don’t really know as the information is not easily accessible. These guys
were pumping out motivational articles about famous people, and life tips and tricks to help you succeed. Is this really news? Who knows, but it’s 100% MEL. This
site was doing so well, so what went wrong?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suspect their to be a simple cause. Notice in the current day, the left sidebar on the MELnewzers site says the ominous acronym, “VEC.” I have seen so many
acronyms throughout my time I don’t even know if I have storage for any more. The handy-dandy sidebar indicates VEC means volunteering and education. These don’t
follow typical HBA acronym naming guidelines, as none of the letters of the acronym in the full name are capitalized. Since there are no parenthesis we can assume
there are no implied letters, there is one “v” so that’s capitalized. The “e” is tricky, I personally think you can’t choose between the two “e”s in volunteering,
as they are right next to each other, so I will take the liberty of assuming the “e” in education is the 2nd letter in VEC. The C has to come after that e, and there
is a c in education and club, and I really can’t figure out what is what. Below the VEC icon it says VEC Club, in which case club is not part of the acronym, but the
blurb indicates VEC means volnteering and education club. Does VEC mean “volunteering and education” club or “volunteering and education club” club? I am so bamboozled.
I’m gonna go with Volunteering EduCation Club, let us know what you guys think in the comments below, we do read all of them! Digging into VEC a little more, it turns
out VEC has their own website and social media accounts. I’ll leave the further digging to you, loyal Hecrenews reader. It looks like VEC has purchased or acquired
MELnewzers in one way or another, and MELnewzers has stopped posting articles/blogs since, maybe. Idk tbh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MELnewzers hasn’t posted since February 16th, 2021, promising one or two posts weekly starting the week after said week. This has not happened. What has VEC done to
MELnewzers? Who knows, but what we do know with the lack of articles is that MELnewzers is no longer a Hecrenews competitor, which is why we are finally revealing the
name to our rival news site. The only thing I can really say is this is mad sus, and I’ve seen a lot of strange things in my time. It should further be noted, that the
articles by Wopps featuring the notorious Monkey Beater have been posted on the MELnewzers blog, but currently are not available, they must have been shutting Monkey
Beater down (which is good, no qualms with that). Winning by default is not the most exhilirating thing, but I think it captures the spirit of our team the most.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well it looks like this is the time for me the wrap up this article. When is the next article coming out? I have no clue. What I do know is this has been Mister Mjir,
popping in and now popping out!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>mister_mjir</name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><category term="Meta" /><summary type="html">Hello hello, it’s ya boi Mister Mjir popping in for another one. Yes it’s been a while but things at out Hecrenews branch have been quite busy, so I didn’t get time to really dig down deep into a story and produce an article about it. Anyways, here’s the scoop.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Safety Seal Malfunction: 15 Reported Attacked by Drunk Ferrets</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2021/07/04/safety-seal-malfunction-fifteen-reported-attacked-by-drunk-ferrets.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Safety Seal Malfunction: 15 Reported Attacked by Drunk Ferrets" /><published>2021-07-04T23:03:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-07-04T23:03:00+00:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2021/07/04/safety-seal-malfunction-fifteen-reported-attacked-by-drunk-ferrets</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2021/07/04/safety-seal-malfunction-fifteen-reported-attacked-by-drunk-ferrets.html">&lt;p&gt;Safety Seals. You know them, you love them, let’s talk about them! We know there’s a whole assortment of fun safety seals, and their main function is to ensure the
item you are opening has not been opened before. Quite an ingenius invention, it took the packaging industry by storm during its inception! We have safety seals
on decks of cards, to know they’re brand new, we have safety seals on bottles, so you can trust that the bottle of substance you are purchasing is fresh of the shelf!
Sometimes safety seals even have some variations, just as the safety ‘bubbles’ on the lids of some food items, like pasta suace. Safety seals play an imporant role in
our society. They let us know things are legit, and ensure we are getting new things, not hand-me-downs. In fact, I would say the society we live in today could not
function without safety seals, and that’s why a safety seal malfunction was so devastating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A business of ferrets were roaming around Chiclayo, and normally they wouldn’t attack people but not today. A local soda company’s safety seals, which were outsourced
to another company, had a major malfunction. Apparently, because of global warming, the safety seal manufacturer had to change the raw materials needed to make the
safety seals, and the new materials were ineffective, because they were so flimsy. The soda company had the keep the safety seal company anonymous, so I was not able
to conduct a further interview. The ferrets walzted into a store and opened up a few cans of soda and drank them. The store owner was in a different room at the time,
but remembers some rattling occuring at the time. The ferrets got drunk on this soda, and apparently it was some experimental soda for a special client, and not for
the general public, much less a random business of ferrets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was only the beginning of the safety seal problems, a further investigation concludes. Safetly seals for various products all over the market were failing, and
the ferrets attacked the owners of those items, it was a strange occurence for sure. One person had a vacuum cleaner box, and the safety seal was not working at all.
The vacuum cleaner could’ve fallen out of the box and rolled out of the car on the way home, that would’ve been dangerous, but the ferrets definetely topped that.
The vacuum cleaner owner preferred to remain anonymous, but I can report he had multiple scratches on his face and arms, and a shattered broom. I am not a ferret
fighting guru, but I don’t think brooms will be effective against a whole business of them. The other 14 stories were similiar, but they all had different items,
ranging from a &lt;a href=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/jekyll/update/2020/08/09/man-invents-device-that-turns-traffic-light-from-red-to-green.html&quot;&gt;traffic controlling device&lt;/a&gt;
to an 870 watt industrial blast furnace, 18 metres, model ARE4004 with side drawers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How were the ferrets stopped? They weren’t. They are continuing to roam the streets of Peru to this day! They are probably sober by this time, and let me tell you from
experience sober ferrets are far better than drunk ferrets. Didn’t know soda could get them drunk, well it was also surprising that squirrels could get drunk from
moldy coconuts, so I don’t know what to expect from animals anymore. For the people in the streets of Chiclayo, watch out for a business of ferrets, and make sure
your safety seals are class A rated or better.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>pablo</name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><category term="News" /><category term="Rops" /><summary type="html">Safety Seals. You know them, you love them, let’s talk about them! We know there’s a whole assortment of fun safety seals, and their main function is to ensure the item you are opening has not been opened before. Quite an ingenius invention, it took the packaging industry by storm during its inception! We have safety seals on decks of cards, to know they’re brand new, we have safety seals on bottles, so you can trust that the bottle of substance you are purchasing is fresh of the shelf! Sometimes safety seals even have some variations, just as the safety ‘bubbles’ on the lids of some food items, like pasta suace. Safety seals play an imporant role in our society. They let us know things are legit, and ensure we are getting new things, not hand-me-downs. In fact, I would say the society we live in today could not function without safety seals, and that’s why a safety seal malfunction was so devastating.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">New Speedreading Tactics to Replace the Old</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2021/06/09/new-speedreading-tactics-to-replace-the-old.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Speedreading Tactics to Replace the Old" /><published>2021-06-09T22:22:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-06-09T22:22:00+00:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2021/06/09/new-speedreading-tactics-to-replace-the-old</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2021/06/09/new-speedreading-tactics-to-replace-the-old.html">&lt;p&gt;Almost a year ago, Valtteri Eva changed the face of the speedreading game with his novel, 500, no, 1000000000 IQ plays. He took to the video
game speedrunning community, the fastest people on the face of the planet, and figured out how to reduce reading time by magnitudes by
extrapolating. If you missed out on the great exploits of Eva, which will go down in history forever, you can find them
&lt;a href=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/jekyll/update/2020/08/29/man-wins-speedreading-competition-with-new-technique.html&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. As with
speedrunning, Eva’s fame did not last for too long, as new players enetered the game to continue finding better tactics to surpass even Eva.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-tactics&quot;&gt;The tactics&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new tactics that have entered the game are diving, judge-extortion, and eidetic memory, and these are the three major technqiues, the
top speed readers use. To review on what speed reading is, it is a intergalatical competition, run by some fancy people, maybe these older
and experienced Hecrenews authors know but not your friendly neighborhood person Pablo, sorry guys. Participants must climb up the ranks
by participating in rounds, which are judged by multiple judges. There are two sections in a round, first a person must read the whole book,
if they chose to do so. There is a nuance in the rules where really you just need to declare that you are done. Afterwards you are not
allowed to look at the book and must wait for the second section. The second section is a comprehension section. The judges ask questions
about the book and the participant must answer the questions correctly. Whoever get more questions right wins the round, if there is a tie,
it is based on who finished the book faster. (There are multiple books per round, you must read all of them, and then answer questions
about all of them)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-is-extrapolation&quot;&gt;What is extrapolation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Extrapolation is exptrapolating what is on the book while reading this. Eva was the pioneer in this strategy and used it as a major
timeskip, stunning the other competitors. It is not skipping the book, but more like writing it yourself giving a few words. You figure
out the rest of the words given a certain amount of words, just like extrapolating in your science class. (Remember to extrapolate, do not
fabricate)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;divining&quot;&gt;Divining&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Divining is one of the greatest techniques out there. I honestly don’t know how this works. The people just know the book, the answers
just seep into their brains. They are forces of nature, they are unstoppable, would I mess with them? Probably not. I don’t know how
people train for this, but most of the users of this method are usually able to predict the future as well. Do they ask a higher being
for assistance? I do not know, but I do know that they get results. Diviners get things done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;judge-extortion&quot;&gt;Judge-Extortion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why read the book anyways, reading is for nerds, is the best way to describe judge extortion. There are many ways to extort a judge.
This is a complex strategy involving psychology, economy, mind games, hijinks, bamboozling, and more fancy words, everything except
for doing anything with the book. At the lower levels, where there is less regulation, bribing a judge is easy. However, as you start to
move up the ranks, it gets increasingly difficult to bribe the judge. Once you get past your country, if your planet does not have a
worldwide currency, simply money may not be enough to bribe all the judges, and this strategy is most effective if all the judges
are bribed. The galactical level is beyond me, I’ve never been there so I don’t even know what kind of currency you would need to bribe
those judges, rare space material?? Although controversial, the main claim seems to be integrity and honesty and honor and pride and that
business, this strategy has had widespread success, especially with those who cannot divine the answers. In some ways it’s better, because
why even try and read when you can just pay to win?!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;eidetic-memory&quot;&gt;Eidetic Memory&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Photographic memory, eidetic memory, same thing, but eidetic sounds fancier. You may be thinking, how can these compete at the higher
levels, divining looks like it will crush this technique. However, divining takes a bit of time to work, although waaaaay less than
actually reading the book. With eidetic memory, competitors can just flip through the pages of all the books. There are many book
flipping techniques dervied from them (note book flipping refers to flipping the pages of the book, not flipping the actual book).
The tricky part for edietic memory people is they must also be geniuses. Sometimes, the questions are in their favor, asking for a specific
detail or asking what’s the nth word on page 56, but sometimes its a comprehension question. To optimize their memory, they must be
comprehending the book at the same time they are memorizing the pages, and that’s some crazy stuff if you ask me! These are the
super-geniuses of the bunch, and pretty rare, however common amongst the cream of the crop speedreaders. You know, I have photographic
memory too, I take out my cell phone, snap a picture, and that’s a photo my phone will remember, photographic memory, never fails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are new techniques being created as I write this article. The most prominent game changer I see is super-extrapolation. This is
leagues above extrapolation, the user extrapolates the entire book given only its title. I can’t even begin to fathom how these people
will do it, but if speedreading gains traction where I’m from (Peru by the way), the whole foundation of society will be shook, I might
have to venture to find where the other Hecrenews journalists are, I don’t think they’re from my planet, much less from Peru.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, these people are constantly changing the game of speedreading, and while Eva’s strategy of extrapolation may be collecting dust, we
can never forget that he is the father of speedreading techniques. He took an uninteresting competition, and made so many more people
interested in it. He has truly done great things for the speedreading community, and the super-extrapolaters plan to upgrade the
extrapolation technique and restore its former glory.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>pablo</name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Almost a year ago, Valtteri Eva changed the face of the speedreading game with his novel, 500, no, 1000000000 IQ plays. He took to the video game speedrunning community, the fastest people on the face of the planet, and figured out how to reduce reading time by magnitudes by extrapolating. If you missed out on the great exploits of Eva, which will go down in history forever, you can find them here. As with speedrunning, Eva’s fame did not last for too long, as new players enetered the game to continue finding better tactics to surpass even Eva.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Reputable News Source Pulls Epic April Fools Prank</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2021/04/30/reputable-news-source-pulls-epic-april-fools-prank.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Reputable News Source Pulls Epic April Fools Prank" /><published>2021-04-30T02:13:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-04-30T02:13:00+00:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2021/04/30/reputable-news-source-pulls-epic-april-fools-prank</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2021/04/30/reputable-news-source-pulls-epic-april-fools-prank.html">&lt;p&gt;This just in. Reputable news source, the Hecrenews, has pulled a massive April Fools prank on its loyal readers. What prank would be so epic? Well, recently, the
Hecrenews hasn’t been posting many articles, and that’s the prank! Can you believe it! Only one article in January and one in February, you can’t get any lower! In
fact, skeptics speculate there were also no articles in March, but only time will tell. Many a time has the Hecrenews had a lack of news. Once it was simple laziness,
once it was an inability to find anything interesting, and once it was problems with the management. The management does seem to be a lot better than what it has
reported to be, there have been 0 reports to HR these past few months, and that’s a 420% decrease! I really do wonder how they manage this, probably being ‘run by the
HBA’ is what gets everyone by. Do they even pay attention? Who knows. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://hecrenet.github.io/update/2021/02/28/new-design.html&quot;&gt;latest article on the hecrenet&lt;/a&gt;
was from all the way back in the end of February, and that was just about the site design update (gotta say, I do love the design though). No updates on Hecrepedia
and the twitter either, what happened to the HBA? Maybe they are just so effective at weeding out the snaxii we aren’t hearing much from them, but this is still rather
disappointing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many critics are not happy with the April Fools joke. For one, it is not even April Fools anymore, critics cite laziness and calling it an April Fools joke is an
excuse to hid it- but brooo, it’s just a prank! Izrail Swanhilde, a local that we interviewd, reported “as the Hecrenews is one of few real media outlets these days,
it is the only thing I read. I read nothing else, heck, I do nothing else! When the articles stopped posting I didn’t know what to do with myself, I was going crazy,
I was driven insane. It was madness, radical, unfathomable! I was sitting in my couch, hitting refresh 24-7 in hopes of a new article. Thank goodness Wopps posted one
a little over a week ago, I do not know if I can adjust to this new life style, it’s like switching from eating three full meals and around the clock snacks to just
eating one bean for the entire day’s meal. Sohrab Patrício turned to other “news” sources, such as MELnewzers, but was struggling to find that Hecrenews quality there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether it is laziness or a prank, who knows, but we do know that the folks at Hecrenews are making big moves. Who knows what’s going to happen next?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>pablo</name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><category term="News" /><category term="Meta" /><summary type="html">This just in. Reputable news source, the Hecrenews, has pulled a massive April Fools prank on its loyal readers. What prank would be so epic? Well, recently, the Hecrenews hasn’t been posting many articles, and that’s the prank! Can you believe it! Only one article in January and one in February, you can’t get any lower! In fact, skeptics speculate there were also no articles in March, but only time will tell. Many a time has the Hecrenews had a lack of news. Once it was simple laziness, once it was an inability to find anything interesting, and once it was problems with the management. The management does seem to be a lot better than what it has reported to be, there have been 0 reports to HR these past few months, and that’s a 420% decrease! I really do wonder how they manage this, probably being ‘run by the HBA’ is what gets everyone by. Do they even pay attention? Who knows. The latest article on the hecrenet was from all the way back in the end of February, and that was just about the site design update (gotta say, I do love the design though). No updates on Hecrepedia and the twitter either, what happened to the HBA? Maybe they are just so effective at weeding out the snaxii we aren’t hearing much from them, but this is still rather disappointing.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hackers, once again, Target Mr. Dobrila</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2021/04/21/hackers-once-again-target-mr-dobrila.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hackers, once again, Target Mr. Dobrila" /><published>2021-04-21T22:45:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-04-21T22:45:00+00:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2021/04/21/hackers-once-again-target-mr-dobrila</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2021/04/21/hackers-once-again-target-mr-dobrila.html">&lt;p&gt;Mr. Isaiah Dobrila is just always in the thick of the action! After making &lt;a href=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/jekyll/update/2020/05/24/man-makes-big-bucks-with-the-help-of-nigerian-prince.html&quot;&gt;big bucks with the help of a Nigerian Prince&lt;/a&gt; and being &lt;a href=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/jekyll/update/2020/08/05/email-hackers-bring-man-closer-to-everyone-in-his-contact-list.html&quot;&gt;confronted by email hackers&lt;/a&gt;, he once again found himself in dire straits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dobrila has been an avid player of hit online multiplayer game Skidibidibop for quite some time now. After jumping into the forest maze for what seemed like minutes but was actually a couple weeks, Dobrila was in danger of losing himself.. once again. Finding something you can get so utterly engrossed in once is uncommon enough, but twice? Guess we shouldn’t put it past Isaiah Dobrila.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, just as he was about to discover the secret behind the Big Bad Boss, Dobrila’s game stuttered. Then it froze. Then it jived, but only for a moment. And finally, it poppped. But not the game. “Working on Updates. 3% Complete. Don’t turn off your computer”. Dobrila was frantic. Did the game save? Would he lose all of his progress? Would he have to spend hours of agony in the forest maze again? He stodd there, in front of his monitor, anxiously watching the percentage go up, darkly muttering several phrases that HAC wouldn’t let me put here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the updating finally finished, Dobrila’s body was stiff for sitting in the same position for hours on end. Nevertheless, he warmed up his creaking joints, ready to get back in the thick of it, battling snaxii and splattery things in his favorite pastime. But Alas! The updates had signed him out of the skidibidibop servers! Now, this wouldn’t be a problem for the normal man, but Isaiah Dobrila is no normal man. In his rush to hop onto and start exploring the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l034nh6VtUQ&quot;&gt;wonderous world&lt;/a&gt; of skidibibdibop, Dobrila had just typed in gibberish as his password and hoped clicking “stay signed in” would save him. Oh boy, was he in a predicament now! All his millions from the Nigerian Prince couldn’t restore his progress. What could he do?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suddenly, Dobrila’s discord dinged. In came a very unsettling message at first, but as Dobrila interacted with this hacker-type (who was last seen &lt;a href=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/jekyll/update/2020/09/29/the-resistance-trying-to-take-down-nit-flex.html&quot;&gt;trying to take down Nit Flex&lt;/a&gt;, wonder what happened to that story?), he realized something. He could use this! Through a sequency of cleverly manipulating messages, Dobrila got the hacker to reveal his own password to him. Genius, if I say so myself. Dobrila, armed with both his login credentials, could now successfully sink the rest of his life into playing that meaningless video game. Hooray!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/cheeky_hacker_dms.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Above are messages sent by Dobrila and SnaxelyLeftButtock_012. Oh, how Dobrila bamboozled that man!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And there goes another happy ending. Don’t you love it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whew, it’s been a while. Don’t expect this to last. Wopps out.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>wopps_minor</name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><category term="News" /><category term="Hacks" /><summary type="html">Mr. Isaiah Dobrila is just always in the thick of the action! After making big bucks with the help of a Nigerian Prince and being confronted by email hackers, he once again found himself in dire straits.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Cars Gain Ability to Text While Drivers Talk</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2021/02/18/cars-gain-ability-to-text-while-drivers-talk.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cars Gain Ability to Text While Drivers Talk" /><published>2021-02-18T22:45:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-02-18T22:45:00+00:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2021/02/18/cars-gain-ability-to-text-while-drivers-talk</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2021/02/18/cars-gain-ability-to-text-while-drivers-talk.html">&lt;p&gt;For many years, drivers have been restricted to the conditions of being unable to talk and text now. They have to drive now and talk and text later, it only allows for
more safety and less accidents, and drivers are beginning to hate driving. What is driving without being able to talk and text. While the future seemed bleak for these
drivers, something strange, unique, revolutionary happened. Cars developed a somewhat pseudo-symbiotic relationship with the drivers, and now they are able to work
together towards the same goal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the first things achieved with the new ability cars gained was the ability for cars to text. The signs on the street only prevent talking and texting, but cars
are smarter than they look and used some boolean logic and algebra to determine that if the drivers are takling OR texting, they won’t be talking AND texting, and
that’s the trick. Drivers can talk all they want, while they’re ever so loyal cars do the texting. The productivity some people experienced this was insane. Tovah Siti
was able to communicate with 34x times as many people, she was able to finish all of the company’s hard labor on the drive to work, and was able to just fool around
during work, but is slated for rapid promotion. Quintilian Najm was able to meet everyone in the city, and won the local race for some governmental position we
don’t really know! Some concerns arise about cars texting. If cars text another car, does it count as the drivers texting? Do the cars have a mind of their own? Is this
ethical? Sustainable? Conservational? Conversational? Those are the big questions we will try to answer, so we sought the man with the answers, a disicple of the
man of destiny: Brian Jones. We contacted Ulisses from a
&lt;a href=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/jekyll/update/2020/11/10/airplanes-have-strange-ability-to-fly.html&quot;&gt;previous article&lt;/a&gt; to see if she knew any car mechanics. The pilot was
very insightful, so we thought a car mechanic could also help. Luckilly for us she knew just the right person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nathalie Arachne. A mechanical genius since she was 3 years old. Able to disassemble clocks, microwaves, vacuum cleaners, and resassemble them within seconds. However,
she sought greater power and turned to the one and only man who can explain. We tried to interview her… “Do you know how these cars work? How are they able to talk.
Apparently they gained this ability, is it like evolving in video games?” “Brain Jones… Brain Jones… Waves…” “Uh… you hear me?” “That tie dye shirt, that look,
his mane…” “So… do you have any coherent comments on these cars?” “Brian, Brian, Brian Jones…”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What does it mean to be a disciple of Brian Jones? What power do you gain? What do you lose (it seems like that would be one’s sanity). This Brian Jones character
has foiled one, now two articles now, he seems to be a force stopping us from reaching the truth. These texting cars will have to be put on hold, for now we must
gather all Hecrenews Journalists, and begin an investigation on Brian Jones.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>mister_mjir</name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><category term="News" /><category term="Driving" /><category term="Technology" /><summary type="html">For many years, drivers have been restricted to the conditions of being unable to talk and text now. They have to drive now and talk and text later, it only allows for more safety and less accidents, and drivers are beginning to hate driving. What is driving without being able to talk and text. While the future seemed bleak for these drivers, something strange, unique, revolutionary happened. Cars developed a somewhat pseudo-symbiotic relationship with the drivers, and now they are able to work together towards the same goal.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Monkeys Preparing to Engage in Battles with Man</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2021/01/28/monkeys-preparing-to-engage-in-battles-with-man.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Monkeys Preparing to Engage in Battles with Man" /><published>2021-01-28T03:18:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-01-28T03:18:00+00:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2021/01/28/monkeys-preparing-to-engage-in-battles-with-man</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2021/01/28/monkeys-preparing-to-engage-in-battles-with-man.html">&lt;p&gt;Return to monke. This is the phrase swarming the internet (ah, not really anymore, you know how that meme economy is constantly changing). Abandon humanity, and
return to monke. Who needs phones, jobs, farms, cities, paved roads, comfy beds, restaruants, and more when you can just abandon it all and return to monke!
Science fairs had to put a new regulation specifically for this, all kids participating were experimenting how they could revert back to a monkey, and the 
Science fair just needed some more variety (although Sheeple Dunnel’s insight on this would be greatly appreciated, seems he switched phone numbers and I wasn’t
in the loop). What’s wrong with monkeys? says non South/South Asian people, in a recent interview conducted by local citizen scientists. Only those people know
the true horror of monkeys, and how dangerous they can be. They may be little, but they can attack you, steal your food, break into your house, and do this all
without facing legal consequences! That is obviously unfair, maybe there are truly merits to returning to monke. That’s besides the point, what we are here to
do today is cover the latest and most important ground-breaking news, monumental events that would make each article important for the history books. And recently,
such an event has taken place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monkeys have begun their offense on man, just look at the evidence! (Photo courtesy of (or stolen from) telegraph.co.uk)
&lt;img src=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/assets/images/monkey_about_to_beat_up_mans.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Rops you can't see the image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monkeys played the fool for this man, distracting him while a member takes advantage of the man’s blind spot, and prepares to beat him down with a stick. This event
should shed light on how monkeys truly behave. These cunning creatures abuse their intelligence to come up with high IQ plays like these. Aradhana Stefan is an
avid anti-monkeyist, who is a (mon)key player (hahaha see what I did there? I’m so funny) in crumbling and taking down the monkey opposition. 1000s of undergound
monkey gangs were put under arrest in Stefan’s tenure, and she plans to keep on going until there is peace. We were able to talk with her shortly, but only shortly
as she is a busy person fighting for our society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Some must venture into the darkness, no longer in the protection of their light, but fight in the darkness to ensure the peace which the light provides. Our
job as anti-monkeyists is to stop monkey opposition. We humans are already so divided against ourselves, just concerened about places of birth, who are parents
are, how much melanin we have, monkeys are using this golden opportunity of man’s struggle with himself to take down man and become the dominant specicies. I
remember reading an article about someone stopping trees from becoming the dominant specicies, and we hold similar beliefs. We try to be as kind as we can to the
monkeys, if we play too rough radical animal activist groups will come and try to take us down. We are fighting hard and nonstop to create a future for humans, 
only when we are united together will monkeys be no more of a threat, but as it stands now we are simply just not ready for that yet.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stefan’s words are very insightful, and just remind us of how many people are working behind the scenes so we can live comfortably. It is truly altruistic, and
is the birthplace of many legends. I myself went into a zone with a mild amount of monkeys, and it wasn’t pretty. I am currently skedaddling outta here before
these monkeys grab a hold of me (and dang are they fast!) This has been Mister Mjir, popping in and now popping out.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>mister_mjir</name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><category term="News" /><summary type="html">Return to monke. This is the phrase swarming the internet (ah, not really anymore, you know how that meme economy is constantly changing). Abandon humanity, and return to monke. Who needs phones, jobs, farms, cities, paved roads, comfy beds, restaruants, and more when you can just abandon it all and return to monke! Science fairs had to put a new regulation specifically for this, all kids participating were experimenting how they could revert back to a monkey, and the Science fair just needed some more variety (although Sheeple Dunnel’s insight on this would be greatly appreciated, seems he switched phone numbers and I wasn’t in the loop). What’s wrong with monkeys? says non South/South Asian people, in a recent interview conducted by local citizen scientists. Only those people know the true horror of monkeys, and how dangerous they can be. They may be little, but they can attack you, steal your food, break into your house, and do this all without facing legal consequences! That is obviously unfair, maybe there are truly merits to returning to monke. That’s besides the point, what we are here to do today is cover the latest and most important ground-breaking news, monumental events that would make each article important for the history books. And recently, such an event has taken place.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hecrenews Hacker Caught</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2021/01/22/hecrenews-hacker-caught.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hecrenews Hacker Caught" /><published>2021-01-22T23:32:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-01-22T23:32:00+00:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2021/01/22/hecrenews-hacker-caught</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2021/01/22/hecrenews-hacker-caught.html">&lt;p&gt;World’s best news source, the Hecrenews, was hacked by a rogue group of hackers. It started when the 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/jekyll/update/2020/12/28/redacted.html&quot;&gt;latest article&lt;/a&gt; was completed removed, all the text, title, about everything. I can’t bother
to remember what it was about so it’s gone. Worst yet, not only did they delete that article, but they prevented Hecrenews from being able to post any new articles,
and this lasted for almost a month! The world almost plunged into chaos without the constant stream of reliable news, instead turning to unreliable, fake, bad,
terrible, radical, wrong, etc. news sites! Luckily our top tech computer whisperers here at Hecrenews not only got out access back, but with the help of PS
(The famous Phone Search and Rescue Squad, which using the Hecrenews search feature I’m sure you can find some articles about)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Hecrenews Computer Magicians (HECMAN) (They might be called something else, idk) had hurried in the development of the Hecrenews, and there was one major bug,
one entrypoint, left unoticed, and the hackers exploited the entry point to break in. They used SSH, IPv6, SHA-256, and whatever other fancy data terms you can
imagine. A trojan horse was deployed, which was meant to delete all content from the Hecrenews, but it was poorly coded and only blocked us from posting articles.
After discussing the topics with Wopps Minor, I had surmised the suspect to be one of the hacker from one of Hector’s
&lt;a href=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/jekyll/update/2020/08/05/email-hackers-bring-man-closer-to-everyone-in-his-contact-list.html&quot;&gt;articles&lt;/a&gt;. The act of selling
anti-snaxe spray instead of snaxe spray is a horror itself, but this hacker cracked Isiah Dobrilla’s account, and no small fry could simply do that to the one
who is in kahoots with a Nigerian prince. I was certain it was this group, but it was all speculation, I could not come to a conclusive answer until I got facts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PS are the expert finders, and they do much more than just phones. Since they haven’t dabbled into too much of technology, HECMAN was apt and eager to assist PS in
searching for the culprits. In a grueling week of coding camp, PS had the fancy tech knowledge to do just about anything HECMAN could. The technology of HECMAN
combined with the searching prowess of PS can only lead to one result: the hackers get caught.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just three days after the coding teaching camp session, PS and HECMAN found the culprits. I wasn’t paying attention when they were talking about subway net gate
masks and hyper text transfer protocol, so I don’t have much content here for you loyal readers, but I do know that they got the job done. The pertaining officials
and even the HBA were notified about this organization. We’re sure these hackers will face the legal consequences, and luckily we won’t have to deal with them!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Writing another article after a while feels whack, this has been Mister Mjir, popping in and now popping out.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>mister_mjir</name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><category term="News" /><summary type="html">World’s best news source, the Hecrenews, was hacked by a rogue group of hackers. It started when the latest article was completed removed, all the text, title, about everything. I can’t bother to remember what it was about so it’s gone. Worst yet, not only did they delete that article, but they prevented Hecrenews from being able to post any new articles, and this lasted for almost a month! The world almost plunged into chaos without the constant stream of reliable news, instead turning to unreliable, fake, bad, terrible, radical, wrong, etc. news sites! Luckily our top tech computer whisperers here at Hecrenews not only got out access back, but with the help of PS (The famous Phone Search and Rescue Squad, which using the Hecrenews search feature I’m sure you can find some articles about)</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[REDACTED]</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2020/12/28/redacted.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[REDACTED]" /><published>2020-12-28T23:32:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-12-28T23:32:00+00:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2020/12/28/redacted</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2020/12/28/redacted.html">&lt;p&gt;[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]
[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]
[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]
[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]
[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]
[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]
[REDACTED]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]
[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]
[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]
[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[REDACTED][REDACTED]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[REDACTED]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[REDACTED]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[REDACTED]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[REDACTED]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[REDACTED]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[REDACTED]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]
[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]
[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]
[REDACTED]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]
[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]
[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>mister_mjir</name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><category term="News" /><summary type="html">[REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED][REDACTED]</summary></entry></feed>