<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-06-05T05:07:32+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Hecrenews</title><entry><title type="html">Timeless Watches</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2024/06/02/timeless-timepieces.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Timeless Watches" /><published>2024-06-02T04:47:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-06-02T04:47:00+00:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2024/06/02/timeless-timepieces</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2024/06/02/timeless-timepieces.html">&lt;p&gt;If you’re a loyal Hecrenews reader, you may know that I’m no stranger to time, especially when time goes wild. No time slowing down or stopping or travel
this article though, today we’re going to be talking about a local businessman and his revolutionary business strategy/model. This entrepreneur is
gonna make it big, he’s gonna make it huge, I know it. Introducing Trist Wawch, a man who has revolutionized the watch industry. All the big brands are
in fear of going bankrupt because Wawch is able to do it all. On top of creating watches at all price points (dirt cheap to billionaire designer
models), Wawch has added his own special flair. A new technique to make his watches stand out from the rest. Timeless watches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of all, what even is a watch? Watch is a verb, it means to look at something. Or at least I think, that’s my own interpretation, now let’s check
out what google and the other big guys have to say. Alright, the folks at Oxford Languages have this to say abot watch, “look at or observe attentively 
over a period of time.” Well, I forgot the period of time bit, but otherwise I was spot on. There are a few other definitions, like to be careful,
but who needs those. Watch can also be a noun, but specifically we are talking about wrist watches. When did the first watch appear? Well, we need to
talk about when time itself appeared. While time was always moving around, right under our noses, we didn’t really have a standard for time. Some groups
of people use the sun for time. The sun usually aligns with our bodies’ natural rhythm. We are awake when the sun is up, and sleep when the sun is down.
At one point in time, lol, we started moving fast. We started moving so fast, that we could move from one place to another, and the sun would still be in relatively
the same position. How were we able to move so fast? Well, we didn’t gain an extra leg. We invented trains! With the advent of trains, we needed to standardize times,
it just made everything a whole lot easier. Then we built our lives around our standardized time, and wrist watches are a neat item you can just slap on to see what
time it is in a glance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, back to how Wawch is revolutionizing the watch industry. Timeless watches. When a watch is timeless, it loses its ability to tell time. Now, I was quite baffled
at this concept, so I interviewed a random guy on the street wearing one of Wawch’s timeless pieces (they’re so popular it wasn’t hard to find a person wearing one).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me: “So, why did you purchase a watch that can’t even tell what the time is? Doesn’t that defeat the purpose of a watch?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Random Guy: “Well, it’s timeless.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me: “Yeah, but what if you wanted to know the time?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Random Guy: “Oh, I wouldn’t know how to read it anyways. Isn’t that what phones are for? I’ll just pull it out of my pocket and quickly check the time, saves me a lot
of time compared to trying to read what the watch says.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me: “So why did you get the watch?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Random Guy: “It looks pretty cool. Doesn’t it look sick?! Since it’s timeless, it never gets old. I think that’s mad rad.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I get Adalbert Bulstrode vibes with this. I thought taking the time out of a watch would make it lose its value, but I guess Wawch’s wrist watches don’t deserve that.
I guess the mechanical motion of a watch will inveitably cause wear, and a timeless watch will truly never get old. The more I think about it, the more brilliant the
concept becomes. Ah yes, timeless watches. Trist Wawch is a genius ahead of my time. A timless watch is not just a fashion statement, it’s a life statement. To make
this article more legit, I’ve interviewed Wawch himself just for completion sake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me: “So, how is business after starting your timless watch collection?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wawch: “Business is booming. And more than ever. Our company is doing amazing. We have so much money, I was able to give my employees 6 month vacations.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me: “Wow, that’s wonderful! Now that sounds like a great company to work at.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wawch: “It sure is, but making watches that meet our standard of quality isn’t easy. The training is a trial of itself, and that’s why we’re the best of the best.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me: “Good stuff, anything else you would like our readers to know. Maybe something inspirational?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wawch: “Well, I hope you can be inspired to buy my new watch collection. These are the series 15Y in scarlet red, everglade green, and brilliant blue. Prices start at
$399, and we can go more if you’d like. Go to your nearest watch store, because it’s probably owned by us! Thanks for your patronage.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not very inspirational, but I think he got away with placing a free ad in our paper. Welp, it’s not like I care. It looks like Wawch’s company is going to be doing
pretty well, so I would place some stocks in his company if I were you. With how much money I get from the boss, it will be impossible for me to buy a timeless piece :(
This has been Mister Mjir, popping in, and now popping out.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>mister_mjir</name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><category term="News" /><category term="Business" /><category term="Fashion" /><summary type="html">If you’re a loyal Hecrenews reader, you may know that I’m no stranger to time, especially when time goes wild. No time slowing down or stopping or travel this article though, today we’re going to be talking about a local businessman and his revolutionary business strategy/model. This entrepreneur is gonna make it big, he’s gonna make it huge, I know it. Introducing Trist Wawch, a man who has revolutionized the watch industry. All the big brands are in fear of going bankrupt because Wawch is able to do it all. On top of creating watches at all price points (dirt cheap to billionaire designer models), Wawch has added his own special flair. A new technique to make his watches stand out from the rest. Timeless watches.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ah the ullet</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2024/05/26/ah-the-ullet.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ah the ullet" /><published>2024-05-26T05:35:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-05-26T05:35:00+00:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2024/05/26/ah-the-ullet</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2024/05/26/ah-the-ullet.html">&lt;p&gt;Ah yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This has been Mister Mjir, popping in and popping out.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>mister_mjir</name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><category term="News" /><category term="Something" /><summary type="html">Ah yes</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Machu Picchu</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2023/06/05/machu-picchu.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Machu Picchu" /><published>2023-06-05T17:53:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-06-05T17:53:00+00:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2023/06/05/machu-picchu</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2023/06/05/machu-picchu.html">&lt;p&gt;Hello all. It’s me, Pablo. It’s been over a year since my last article, and a lot has happened in that time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my &lt;a href=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/jekyll/update/2022/03/16/cliff-hotels.html&quot;&gt;last article&lt;/a&gt;, I was in a cliff
hotel. Just a stop in the journey to go and see the great Machu Picchu; however, this journey did not have smooth sailing in mind. We began the hike to Machu Picchu, but after about two hours, the conditions in the mountians
became unsafe for travelling. We had to take shelter in a cave we found. We could not head back the way we came
either, the mountain conditions were not good all around the Machu Picchu area. Apparently, there were mines scattered throughout the area, and our communication tools were limited so we could not get any information on why. All we had was a radio which our tour guide was holding onto. For the next few months, we would be living life in this cavern we found.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/assets/images/cavern_life.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cave&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made some new friends in the cave. The most notable was a llama named Sanchez Ronaldo. Sanchez Ronaldo was the life of our party. We could have met a terrible fate to many reasons, but Sanchez Ronaldo ensured boredom would not be one of them. For months, that llama kept on entertaining us throughout the whole day. It’s hard to imagine how, in a not-so-large-cave, a llama could keep us entertained, but Sanchez was able to it. Everything from singing to dancing, Sanchez Ronaldo was a master of. One day he even pulled out a unicycle and began juggling while riding it. Sanchez Ronaldo was truly a llama who was larger than life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/assets/images/sanchez_ronaldo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;llama&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our time with Sanchez Ronaldo was not to last. One day, about 7-9 months into our stay, we ran out of food. There were children on the tour, so we could not even go a day without food. We were at a loss on what to do, when Sanchez Ronaldo proposed an idea so radical, it shook the very foundations of the world we were living in. “Baaaaaaa.” Sanchez Ronaldo was offering up himself as sacrifice, for our survival. We weren’t going to allow this, but after a few hours and the crying of the children, we realized there was no other choice. We ate Sanchez Ronaldo, and we made sure nothing was wasted. That night was the hardest night of the whole cavern stay. Except the children, no one was able to sleep. A few days later, when our food supply ran out, we were finally saved by a Peru rescue organization. We continued on our journey to Machu Picchu, after leaving a tribute for Sanchez Ronaldo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hike to Machu Picchu was not far from the cave, but I could not believe my eyes when we got there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/assets/images/machu_picchu_heist.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;uh-oh&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machu Picchu was being stolen! A helicopter just yanked it out of the ground and was taking it to who knows where! No wonder the mountain conditions were unsafe, these vile criminals were trying to steal Machu Picchu for months! I was simply aghast and had no ounce of energy left in me to do anything about it. I was just going to watch as one of our country’s sacred mounument was being robbed. Then, in the sky, I see a faint image of a llama. My eyes were definitely playing tricks on me, but I swear it was Sanchez Ronaldo. He phased into the helicopter, and after a few seconds, it exploded! Machu Picchu fell to the ground, right where it had been for centuries. What I witnessed was something of legends, these are the mythical stories I learned about as a child. The spirit of Sanchez Ronaldo just saved Machu Picchu! I am now working with a local author to write a novel about Sanchez Ronaldo and his legendary exploits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also finally got to finally see Machu Picchu. As a Peruvian myself, 4.5/5.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>pablo</name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><category term="News" /><category term="Crime" /><summary type="html">Hello all. It’s me, Pablo. It’s been over a year since my last article, and a lot has happened in that time.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Anti-Alcoholics Anonymous</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2022/08/03/aaa.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Anti-Alcoholics Anonymous" /><published>2022-08-03T22:48:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-08-03T22:48:00+00:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2022/08/03/aaa</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2022/08/03/aaa.html">&lt;p&gt;Many people have heard of AA, alcoholics anonymous. This group is committed to helping people quit or lesson their alcohol addictions. There are many chapters
everywhere, where people can have a safe place to share their stories and be around other people who are on their journey to abstinence. This is a great thing, an
organization helping people to change their habits (only if they want to change their habits ofc!) and providing a safe space to people. We’re all good on that, but
of course as a Hecrenews journalist, I knew there was more to the story. After a few days of searching, man was I right! This group is very obscure, not many people
know about it, but it sure does exist. They are called AAA, Anti-Alcoholics Anonymous. There are for people who are so good at abstaining for alcohol, they have
difficulties trying to drink it. Some of these people are responsible people, and want to enjoy their life a little bit, but they are unable to drink alochol. Whether
it’s spilling the alcohol so it doesn’t get poured into a cup, the inability to open the mouth when the bottle/cup is right in front of it, or rejecting the alcohol
by spitting it out as soon as it enters the mouth, these denizens of society needed their own group to help overcome their problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The leader of the local AAA chapter is Love Choolla. Choolla has wanted to ‘sip the drip’ (idk why the kids call it that these days…) ever since she was of legal age
(for drinking, ofc!). “First of all, let me set a few things straight about AAA. Everything things AA is better than AAA, because just like the batteries, AA is bigger
than AAA. But what these people don’t know is that AA and AAA batteries have the same voltage of 1.5 volts!!! We are just as important as AA, and in my opinion, we
have it harder because we have less people. A smaller community always has it more difficult, and we also have less data and experiences to help us overcome our
challenges. To this day, we haven’t been able to cure a single person of extreme abstinence.” Choolla let me attend one AAA meeting so I could get a better picture
of what goes down in the organization. I saw people from all walks of life, and some people weren’t even able to walk! Today there was a new member joining the
organization, a bonus for me so I could report more things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Hello everyone, my name is Rink D’Cant. I haven’t been able to drink alcohol since my high school prom, when I was first introduced to it. Now thankfully, I’m
fortunate I have been afflicted with this condition then, because it wouldn’t have been a smart decision to start drinking then. The problem is now I’m at the proper
age and my body can handle it. I just want to drink a few fluid ounces of alcohol every friday to cool down when my week ends, is that so wrong? Everytime I pick up
a glass with alcohol, I drop it. Usually, I can’t even pick it up, it’s like Thor’s hammer. Thank you guys for letting me join you, and I hope one day I can ‘sip the
drip.’” (Why do they say that, idk). After D’Cant’s introduction (and can I just say my man has such a fire name, legend) the members all tried to drink alcohol. Some
people tried sticking out their tongues into a glass of alochol if they couldn’t lift it up. However, everyone’s tongues just retracted back in before touching
the drinks. About 15 more minutes were spent as I sadly watched the people fail to drink alcohol after relenteless perseverance, I admire their grit. “OMG, LOOK!” said
Chooolla. One person was able to get some alcohol into their mouth, this was a breakthrough! They were about to swallow it too, but they spat it back into their cup.
“Dang it! I got to taste it, but I didn’t get to drink it!” Everyone just remained on standby for a minute, and the members decided to end the meeting for the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I asked Choolla if there was anything else she wanted to let the folks at home know. “Everyday we are struggling with out problems, and most of the time we just get
laughed at. People don’t think our reality is important, and our misfortunes become other people’s entertainment. This viewpoint needs to stop, maybe they are not
your problems, but that doesn’t mean you can laugh at us. You don’t really know what it’s like until you walk in someone else’s shoes.” Powerful words from Choolla,
I’m sure her sentiment doesn’t only apply to AAA, but people with problems all around the world. Before laughing at someone’s problem or situation, why not lend a
helping hand instead? Well, I’m just a reporter at the end of the day, just gotta please the boss. Anywho, with one breakthrough, I’m sure this local AAA chapter is
on their way to get the first AAA member to drink alcohol, and then start a new era for the AAA where they can actually cure people and help them start drinking
alcohol. This has been Mister Mjir, popping in and popping out.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>mister_mjir</name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><category term="News" /><category term="Health" /><summary type="html">Many people have heard of AA, alcoholics anonymous. This group is committed to helping people quit or lesson their alcohol addictions. There are many chapters everywhere, where people can have a safe place to share their stories and be around other people who are on their journey to abstinence. This is a great thing, an organization helping people to change their habits (only if they want to change their habits ofc!) and providing a safe space to people. We’re all good on that, but of course as a Hecrenews journalist, I knew there was more to the story. After a few days of searching, man was I right! This group is very obscure, not many people know about it, but it sure does exist. They are called AAA, Anti-Alcoholics Anonymous. There are for people who are so good at abstaining for alcohol, they have difficulties trying to drink it. Some of these people are responsible people, and want to enjoy their life a little bit, but they are unable to drink alochol. Whether it’s spilling the alcohol so it doesn’t get poured into a cup, the inability to open the mouth when the bottle/cup is right in front of it, or rejecting the alcohol by spitting it out as soon as it enters the mouth, these denizens of society needed their own group to help overcome their problems.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ricky The Ravenous Bovine</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2022/07/31/ricky-the-ravenous-bovine.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ricky The Ravenous Bovine" /><published>2022-07-31T03:05:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-07-31T03:05:00+00:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2022/07/31/ricky-the-ravenous-bovine</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2022/07/31/ricky-the-ravenous-bovine.html">&lt;p&gt;Mara Wilbur runs a traditional family farm. Now, this is not just any small traditional family farm, this farm was run by McDonald; that’s right, Old McDonald. That
was many generations ago, and not many people know about the current status of the farm. When Old McDonald ran the farm, he revolutionized how farming work. The man
created a whole new ‘field’ (🤣 🤣 🤣) and saved so many lives. The name of Old McDonald was spread far and wide, kids today even know about him! Anywho, this isn’t
an article about the legend and greatness of Old McDonald, this is about his farm now. These days, no one even knows about the McDonald farm, it still exists though.
The current descendant of Old McDonald running the farm is Mara Wilbur, wife of Thomas Wilbur. Today’s story is not even about Mara Wilbur, it’s about a character
who I believe is even more interesting. This mischevious mule, this cunning cattle, this malevolent milk-producer. Ricky The Ravenous Bovine. Ricky is a menace to the
fields, a terror to the barnyard, and a force of nature even Buddha fears. Today, we’re gonna learn a little bit about Ricky (and hopefully I survive to tell the tale
😬).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of all, here is a picture of Ricky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/assets/images/ravenous_ricky.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ravenous Ricky Picture&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ricky is a Belgian Blue Cow, a BBC for short. The BBC is a breed of beef cattle from Belgium, and it might also be known as &lt;em&gt;Race de la Moyenne et Haute Belique&lt;/em&gt;. Omg,
that sounds so cool!!! Another name for it is dikbil, but &lt;em&gt;Race de La Moyenne et Haute Belique&lt;/em&gt;, man what a name! Now, we gotta talk about Ricky’s muscles. Ufff, my man
Ricky over there has some heft. You don’t want him to catch you during a theft! Ricky is always stopped by security for carrying his ‘guns’ everywhere. The pro-breeders
call Ricky’s muscular madness ‘double-muscling.’ This is a phenotype is something the cows inherit, and it increases the amount of muscle fibers, instead of the
individual muscle fibers. It’s hyperplasia vs hypertrophy. Now this is true for all cows like Ricky, what makes Ricky so devious? Well, we’re about to find that out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ricky is a rebel. Most farmers are scared of wolves that would eat their sheep, but Wilbur is scared of Ricky the most. He is temperamental, violent, vicious, cunning,
and much more. Ricky gets what he wants, and there is no one (yet) who can stop Ricky. One day Ricky was caught bullying the pigs. Another day he was seen stealing
eggs from some hens. This Tuesday Ricky hopped the fence and went into a china shop, and boy did he cause some damage there. Ricky is just a straight up delinquent,
downright nasty. He is a menace to the fields, and to this day has not been tamed. Wilbur even called PS to try and tame Ricky, and this was the first job PS ever
had to decline. They knew Ricky was out of their league. Wilbur was losing hope, and she started posting flyers for help. After two months, Wilbur was about to quit
the farm, end the legacy of Old McDonald, but luckily Wilbur found the hope needed to keep the Old McDonald legacy alive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bovine Blackmailer. An expert in teh field, although quite arcane. Many don’t even know the Bovine Blackmailer exists, but the Bovine Blackmailer can find dirt on
any bovine and submit them to do the will of the client. Once the Bovine Blackmailer saw Wilbur’s flyer on the local bulletin board, all it took was one phone call
to secure the deal. Bovine Blackmailer was about to embark on another mission. Unlike PS, the Bovine Blackmailer was unfazed by the terrors of Ricky, the Blackmailer
just went to work finding all the dirt possible on Ricky. He even hired a man to go to Ricky, and literally scrape all the dirt of him! Now that’s the kind of
diligence a blackmailer needs to really find some good dirt. One day, Wilbur received an envelope in the mail. The job was complete, the Bovine Blackmailer had done
the job. Wilbur left the envelope near Ricky, and proceeded to watch from afar. Ricky opened the envelope (of course he knows how, he is built different), and saw
many photos. There weren’t actually &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; many photos, but Ricky did not like what he was seeing in the photos. Ricky, for the first time in his life, looked
scared. What exactly did the Bovine Blackmailer find? I will never know, even Wilbur does not know. Ricky destroyed the photos, no one else should ever see what
was in those photos. The Bovine Blackmailer wasn’t just a rural myth, it’s a real entity, and a dangerous one too! Luckily, the client usually ends up satistfied,
and the Bovine Blackmailer never works for a bovine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These days Ricky is behaving himself and Mara Wilbur is having a much better time at the farm! She is going to continue farming for the rest of her life, now that’s a
happy ending. I know where I’m gonna get my food from now. I’m just glad no one got hurt because of Ricky (except for those pigs probably), those muscles really
are packing quite the punch. This has been Mister Mjir, popping in and now popping out.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>mister_mjir</name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><category term="News" /><category term="Animals" /><summary type="html">Mara Wilbur runs a traditional family farm. Now, this is not just any small traditional family farm, this farm was run by McDonald; that’s right, Old McDonald. That was many generations ago, and not many people know about the current status of the farm. When Old McDonald ran the farm, he revolutionized how farming work. The man created a whole new ‘field’ (🤣 🤣 🤣) and saved so many lives. The name of Old McDonald was spread far and wide, kids today even know about him! Anywho, this isn’t an article about the legend and greatness of Old McDonald, this is about his farm now. These days, no one even knows about the McDonald farm, it still exists though. The current descendant of Old McDonald running the farm is Mara Wilbur, wife of Thomas Wilbur. Today’s story is not even about Mara Wilbur, it’s about a character who I believe is even more interesting. This mischevious mule, this cunning cattle, this malevolent milk-producer. Ricky The Ravenous Bovine. Ricky is a menace to the fields, a terror to the barnyard, and a force of nature even Buddha fears. Today, we’re gonna learn a little bit about Ricky (and hopefully I survive to tell the tale 😬).</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Skip Class or Take the Pass?</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2022/07/24/skip-class-or-take-the-pass.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Skip Class or Take the Pass?" /><published>2022-07-24T03:05:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-07-24T03:05:00+00:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2022/07/24/skip-class-or-take-the-pass</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2022/07/24/skip-class-or-take-the-pass.html">&lt;p&gt;Let’s not waste time. Skip class or take the pass, the classic dilemma. Do you be a rowdy, straight up raucous heathen and just dip class, or do you follow the
rules and take the pass? You don’t wanna be a nerd following the rules, but is being a delinquent really worth the risks? I don’t know much about business, but
let’s delve into the risks and rewards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;skipping-class&quot;&gt;Skipping Class&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Skipping class, it’s classic. Truly timeless. Ever since classes existed, people have been skipping classes. The point of skipping a class is to not take it. Sometimes,
there are just better things to do. Go to the mall, go to the park, watch a movie, run your business, cure cancer (let’s not lie, learning about John Donne’s
&lt;em&gt;The Flea&lt;/em&gt; is one of the best parts of your English class, but it probably won’t help you solve cancer). Here’s the problem, in some countries and some states, children
are required to attend school. A skipper’s biggest enemy, truancy. Children can actually get punished for skipping school. Going to court, failing classes, it’s a big
mess. The trick about skipping is to do it so you won’t get in trouble. Skipping class with impunity is truly a dream. If everyone could skip class, there wouldn’t be
any point. Because skipping class is something one is not supposed to do, that’s what makes it exciting. There is a certain feeling you get when you know you’re
breaking the rules. It’s a complicated topic so we will come back to this. Sometimes skipping is ethical, especially if you are taking a class just for the credit, or
a blow-off class. However, there are some legendary courses one must never skip, and yet some students will still get rowdy and skip these classes. Anywho, don’t
worry about skipping because we will come back to it, let’s discuss taking a pass for some time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;taking-the-pass&quot;&gt;Taking the Pass&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘May I use the bathroom?’ ‘It’s January.’ Getting a pass excuses you from a class. You obtain permission to escape class and go and do your own stuff. Here’s the catch,
you’ll only get 5 minutes of that sweet sweet respite. How will you optimize that time? You could maybe use communication applications to time ‘going to the bathroom’
at the same time to chat with friends, or maybe you just actually need to use the bathroom. Having a pass is good, but you always have to be on the lookout for
E = vB, that’s right, the Hall Monitor. Those sneaky little buggers are always there at the worst times looking to bust you for skipping class. Skipping class by taking
a pass and getting caught is much worse than simply skipping class. If you take the pass too much, your teacher will notice and may prevent you from skipping class. The
legal method does have such a stingy regulation, I don’t think it’s worth it. However, if you know how to optimize those 5 minutes, you should still be able to accomplish
some great stuff. If you’re lucky with your teacher, you may be able to even get away with 30 minutes without being noticed. A true stealth mission, and by following the
‘regulations,’ you won’t have any bad marks on your record.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;other-notes&quot;&gt;Other Notes&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a strategy to give total escape. If you get your parents on board, you can get a pass for skipping any class. You don’t need a doctor’s note if you were only
‘sick’ for a day or two, that’s because you’re not supposed to see a doctor unless you have either something really severe or symptoms for three days. If you can get a
note from your parents, you have the legendary pass. You can skip entire days. However, sometimes you will still need to do the work assigned to you. If you skip out on
your assignments, you might find yourself getting 0s and you could fail the class. That means not only will you have to retake it if there are core requirements, but you
will not be getting credit for this. Your grade point average may be hit, but if you’re focused on the bigger things in life then this shouldn’t be a worry. Truancy court
will probably be your worst nightmare. Time is of the essence, and it’s up to you to make the right decisions to get time. Once you get time, then you just need to figure
out how to make the most of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope this article gave you some insight. This has been Mister Mjir, popping in and now popping out.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>mister_mjir</name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><category term="News" /><category term="Education" /><category term="Crime" /><summary type="html">Let’s not waste time. Skip class or take the pass, the classic dilemma. Do you be a rowdy, straight up raucous heathen and just dip class, or do you follow the rules and take the pass? You don’t wanna be a nerd following the rules, but is being a delinquent really worth the risks? I don’t know much about business, but let’s delve into the risks and rewards.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Man Never Has to Shower Again After Turning Off Dirt Respawn</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2022/07/22/man-never-has-to-shower-again-after-turning-off-dirt-respawn.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Man Never Has to Shower Again After Turning Off Dirt Respawn" /><published>2022-07-22T03:37:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-07-22T03:37:00+00:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2022/07/22/man-never-has-to-shower-again-after-turning-off-dirt-respawn</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2022/07/22/man-never-has-to-shower-again-after-turning-off-dirt-respawn.html">&lt;p&gt;What’s up rapscallions? Today we got an exciting story to keep you on the edge of your seat. Do you hate showering? I mean, sometimes a warm shower is nice, but
stay too long and you’re wasting water. It’s a waste of water &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; a waste of time! Imagine how big your side hustle could be if you used your shower time for that
instead of showering! Hower Tashe is one man who despises showering. He revels it, absolutely disgusts showering. It’s a complete waste of time, but he has to do it
to stay clean. If he’s too smelly, he’ll be fired from work, and then he won’t be able to live in his apartment anymore. Even worse, he’ll lose access to the internet,
and this is truly terrifying. Not having an income source sure is tuff, but it’s not my problem. As a Hecrenews journalist, our job is to straight up get dirty and
find the truth, no matter what it is. Losing work is one thing, but Tashe could (most likely will) lose all his social status. No one wants to hang out with the stinky
guy anyways, Tashe could even lose his date! Being dirty is a huge problem, but showering (or taking a bath) seemed to be the only way to get rid of this problem, and
not wanting to shower only makes this a catch 22! Anyways, Tashe was more than annoyed with having to clean himself everyday, so he looked for alternative methods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First Tashe thought he could simply not get dirty. This was impossible. Everwhere he went, he got dirty. Contact with people, objects, air, food. The dirt, grime, and
stink was out to relentlessly get Tashe. After a week of failing to stay clean, Tashe concluded the ‘simply not get dirty,’ method does not work. In fact, research
from a new study indicate 99% of high school students become dirty, but head of SAR Sheeple Dunnel has yet to review this study, so who knows how accurate it may be 🤷. Tashe wasn’t
ready to give up, he was the man who went livid after even thinking about showers, after all. Tashe went ahead and invented a new type of fabric that instantly
vaporized any type of harmful bacteria. After wearing this for three days, Tashe saw no new results. He just burned up the fabric and threw the notes in the trash.
So sad, maybe he could’ve used it for other things but it was a failed invention, after all. Tashe realized even if he blocked out all external sources of dirt, his
own body will produce it. Oh, what misfortune! How Tashe’s own body betrayed him. Tashe was furious, and decided he needed a few days (and a good whiskey) to cool off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tashe’s brain was running out of creative juice, so he realized he had to go low to stop this problem. Yes, he had to break his moral code. Tashe was going to learn
Computer Science, what Tashe believed to be mankind’s enemy. Tashe also disliked computer science, he was fine with using computers, but knowing that AI and machine
learning could possibly lead to a terminator, Tashe didn’t want to take his chances. Anyways, Tashe buckled down and started the grind. Man was becoming a sigma male,
and one day, he made a breakthrough. Tashe had coded so much, he was able to figure out how to turn off dirt respawn for him. How did he do it? I don’t know, but he
must’ve been a genius. Now he only had to take one last shower, and see if his code worked. One day passed, then two, then three, and soon a whole month! Tashe did not
have to take a single shower in this time period. The dirt just wouldn’t materialize, it couldn’t. Tashe’s shower 0-death’d the dirt and it couldn’t respawn. Here
is rare footage of what the dirt saw.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/assets/images/whats_up_hay_man_oh_oops_you_died.png&quot; alt=&quot;Death Screen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tashe is now living the time of his living. He started his side hustle of packaging stray leaves and clocked in at 30 thousand in the last quarter. Tashe is making
so much bank, just from the time he gained not taking a shower! Now that’s called hustling. I’ll (probably not) cover Tashe’s leaf packaging business in a future
article, but Tashe has made his impact on the world. Let’s just hope the admins don’t catch wind of this, that may cause some problems for Tashe. Anyways, what
an inspriational story. This has been Mister Mjir, popping in and now popping out.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>mister_mjir</name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><category term="News" /><category term="Health" /><summary type="html">What’s up rapscallions? Today we got an exciting story to keep you on the edge of your seat. Do you hate showering? I mean, sometimes a warm shower is nice, but stay too long and you’re wasting water. It’s a waste of water and a waste of time! Imagine how big your side hustle could be if you used your shower time for that instead of showering! Hower Tashe is one man who despises showering. He revels it, absolutely disgusts showering. It’s a complete waste of time, but he has to do it to stay clean. If he’s too smelly, he’ll be fired from work, and then he won’t be able to live in his apartment anymore. Even worse, he’ll lose access to the internet, and this is truly terrifying. Not having an income source sure is tuff, but it’s not my problem. As a Hecrenews journalist, our job is to straight up get dirty and find the truth, no matter what it is. Losing work is one thing, but Tashe could (most likely will) lose all his social status. No one wants to hang out with the stinky guy anyways, Tashe could even lose his date! Being dirty is a huge problem, but showering (or taking a bath) seemed to be the only way to get rid of this problem, and not wanting to shower only makes this a catch 22! Anyways, Tashe was more than annoyed with having to clean himself everyday, so he looked for alternative methods.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Emoji Story</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2022/07/20/emoji-story.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Emoji Story" /><published>2022-07-20T03:37:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-07-20T03:37:00+00:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2022/07/20/emoji-story</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2022/07/20/emoji-story.html">&lt;p&gt;Literature is constantly evolving, it’s a field which will always be relevant. There are many people who have pushed the boundaries of literature. William
Shakespeare, Edgar Allan Poe, Associated Members of the Hecretary Bird Association
(who are &lt;a href=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/jekyll/update/2020/08/02/update-on-the-m-and-m.html&quot;&gt;still working on that book&lt;/a&gt;. Now, we are living in a revolution, a new
height of literature is being reached.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Witness this masterpiece.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/assets/images/a_picture_is_a_thousand_words_but_these_emojis_can_express_so_much_more_i_feel_so_englightened.png&quot; alt=&quot;Epic story&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now &lt;a href=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/jekyll/update/2021/07/20/getting-your-goat.html&quot;&gt;my last tackle with tough literature&lt;/a&gt; was a lot, but this passage has so much more
depth. It’s wrong to call it a passage, this has the worth of a whole series of novels. The author bit can have an entire article on its own, I’ll condense this for
your viewing experience. First there is the profile picture of a lazy red panda loafing around on a tree branch. The art style, the expression, there is so much
weight and character to this image. You can tell more from the author with this profile picture compared to a headshot of a person, in fact, this piece of writing is
so phenomenal, I wouldn’t be surprised if the red panda in the picture is the actual author. Then there is the name. ‘Baddest Rumbler Cat :sunglasses:’. I don’t know
how to escape the colons, so looks like I’ll be stuck with the sunglasses emoji, but it should be colon-sunglasses-colon. Anyways, what a name. I am impressed, there
is so much meaning behind this name. Combined with the profile picture, I am astonished. This is not just any cat, but it is the Baddest Rumbler Cat, and it’s so bad
and has so much style, sunglasses is a part of its name!!! I don’t know what exactly rumbling entails, but I’m sure this is the baddest cat that rumbles. This is a
great figure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now onto the story. It begins with *salvador. Usually, stories begin with an exposition, setting up the context for the story. However, in text talk, an asterisk
usually indicates a correction, whether you are correcting your own message or someone else’s. What exactly is Baddest Rumbler Cat :sunglasses: trying to tell with
the first line? I am not qualified enough to tell, I’m just a journalist. Afterwards, the Cat sends a picture of a potted plant, and there are two responses to the
plant, both being the ‘yum’ emoji. This potted planted must be delicious, or at least that’s what I infer from it. Maybe the plant is from El Salvador, or maybe
salvador means something else on its own. Salvador means saviour, or messiah in Catalan, Spanish, and Portuguese. I can provide this information, but I really
cannot help you decipher what it means, BRC 😎 is too great of a writer for me to figure this out. Anyways, next there is a fire. A heart is engulfed in the fire.
Then there is a fire extinguisher, it puts out the fire and the heart is back to normal. Uh-oh! Watch out, there is a fencer. The fencer pokes at the heart, and breaks
it. Oh, what a tragic tale, it hurts even my heart! Is this a love story, a tragedy, a comment on the current world? I will never know, maybe it’s all of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The heart has gone through so much. It was blazing! Now this could be due to passion, in a positive sense, or it could’ve been like a house fire, in a tragic sense.
All we can infer is eventually, that fire died out, and the heart returned to normal. What is the significane of the potted plant before the heart? What is the
significance of salvador and how do they all relate? Maybe salvador means there is no saviour, or it could mean the story takes place in El Salvador. What we do
know, is at the end of the story, the heart is broken. This is what is so beautiful about this story, it can mean so many different things depending on your outlook
and perspective. Each picture on its own is worth a thousand words, when you combine multiple pictures together, you have what’s basically a book. Let’s observe
the story from a romantic view, like with &lt;em&gt;Romeo and Juliet&lt;/em&gt;. There is a burning passion, probably falling in love. After some time, things begin to cool down and
the lustful heart has calmed, but it is still a heart and still has feelings. However, tragedy strikes and either the lovee or an outside force swiftly strikes the
heart, and all that’s left is a broken heart. This is so sad. Now to get even sadder, we can observe the story through the lens of a tragedy, like &lt;em&gt;Macbeth&lt;/em&gt;. Natural
tragedy strikes, maybe environmental or societal, and someone gets caught up in it. It hurts, but there is light at the end of the tunnel, and the tragedy is
eventually overcome. The person has grown from this, stronger than ever, but life is not up to that person. The fencer, representing even greater tradgedy, strikes!
This time, the heart is broken for good. Overcoming one kind of adversity may make you stronger, but if you live in the biggest lake, you’ve never seen the ocean.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am [REDACTED] and this is sooo deep. I can’t wait to read more from BRC 😎. In the meantime, I will keep on reading this and learn more about life from it.
This has been Mister Mjir, popping in and now popping out.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>mister_mjir</name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><category term="News" /><category term="Writing" /><summary type="html">Literature is constantly evolving, it’s a field which will always be relevant. There are many people who have pushed the boundaries of literature. William Shakespeare, Edgar Allan Poe, Associated Members of the Hecretary Bird Association (who are still working on that book. Now, we are living in a revolution, a new height of literature is being reached.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">February 31st Part 3</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2022/07/16/february-thirty-first.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="February 31st Part 3" /><published>2022-07-16T04:08:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-07-16T04:08:00+00:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2022/07/16/february-thirty-first</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2022/07/16/february-thirty-first.html">&lt;p&gt;What’s up guys, it’s been a bit… Anyways, I know you loyal Hecrenews readers have been at the edge of your seats, waiting for this part 3 since part 2 was
released on April 17. The wait is over, because now the article is finally here. Some bad news guys, my memory’s been bad lately, this must be the consequence of
not writing in a bit. Anyways, we’re gonna have to pad this a bit, let’s start by dropping a quick link to part one and part two ;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/jekyll/update/2022/03/20/february-thirty-first.html&quot;&gt;Part one&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/jekyll/update/2022/04/17/february-thirty-first.html&quot;&gt;Part two&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alright, time to get back into the action. Time began returning to normal with the precense of Adalbert Bulstrode, my man is a legend. Anyways, I noticed someone
I knew walking admist the spectators, why, that’s Isiah Dobrilla! How could I forget! I thought he was zapped along with the head of SAR, Sheeple Dunnell and
Brian Jones, but I guess he was a bit farther away so he just teleported to the crowd. Anyways, you would think there was an epic battle, but no. During his ‘time’,
in the void where space and time is unknown, Adalbert Bulstrode discovered much more physics than what any man knows. He had the knowledge to create the future the
way he wanted it to be written, or at least that’s what I want to think, let me be a fanboy. Oops, I’m supposed to be a journalist, ummmm…. don’t tell anyone, okay?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bulstrode wasted no time in trapping Brain Jones in a ‘Physics Prison’, he called it. He pulled out this contraption from his belt, it was a small cube, and, using
projectile motion, he perfectlly threw the box onto Brian Jones. Brain Jones was sealed inside the box, I asked Bulstrode how it worked but he ensured me I wouldn’t
understand, and even if I wrote it down, no one would be able to understand it. He did tell me there would be a lot of bots inside the box, but I have no clue what
he’s on, I mean what he’s talking about. :{| Then the most unfortunate even took place. Bulstrode told me he had to return to the space time void, for two reasons.
One was that the Physics Prison could not contain Brain Jones forever, he would eventually escape, and Bulstrode just wanted to study it more. Such dedication to
science, if only I was as dedicated to journalism… However, he left me with a better communication device to give to the SAR team, so that was pretty cool. Anyways,
he left quickly, he is a busy man after all, and everyone was in confusion and disarray. Once everyone got back to their senses, Sheeple Dunnell had to go back to
Wah Turtistin to help him out, and Isiah Dobrilla stayed to watch the match.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone was hyped up for the match between Shroops the Almighty and King Louie to continue, but we got scammed. Because of the confusion of the events, the match
would be postponed till February 32nd!!! What was this?!?!?! Hopefully, since it was February 31st, it wouldn’t be that long of a wait. I went hope and took a nap,
but that nap turned into a sleep. When I woke up the next day, the date showed March 1st! I got scammed, February 32nd was skipped, and now I will have to try my
luck again next year! Oh, woe is me, why do I always get such bad luck. I still have my ticket, and will be waiting for their epic match. In the meanwhile, you can
count on our team at the Hecrenews to keep you updated on Shroops the Almighty, and possibly King Louie if we can find his location. This has been Mister Mjir,
popping in and now popping out.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>mister_mjir</name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><category term="News" /><category term="Scandal" /><summary type="html">What’s up guys, it’s been a bit… Anyways, I know you loyal Hecrenews readers have been at the edge of your seats, waiting for this part 3 since part 2 was released on April 17. The wait is over, because now the article is finally here. Some bad news guys, my memory’s been bad lately, this must be the consequence of not writing in a bit. Anyways, we’re gonna have to pad this a bit, let’s start by dropping a quick link to part one and part two ;)</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">February 31st Part 2</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2022/04/17/february-thirty-first.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="February 31st Part 2" /><published>2022-04-17T00:35:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-04-17T00:35:00+00:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2022/04/17/february-thirty-first</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2022/04/17/february-thirty-first.html">&lt;p&gt;Hey guys, it’s been a while. I’m still afflicted by the procrastinatovirus. Doctors have been saying its incurable. Anyways, that’s a story for another time.
If you don’t know about this February 31st stuff, be sure to check out
&lt;a href=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/jekyll/update/2022/03/20/february-thirty-first.html&quot;&gt;part 1&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where we left off, the fated fight between Shroops and King Louie was abruptly ceased by the apperance of Brain Jones and head of Hecrenews SAR, Sheeple
Dunnell. Four formidable foes now stood in the boxing ring, and the fight was only beginning. Sheeple Dunnell had a flow-meter from the
&lt;a href=&quot;https://hecrenews.github.io/jekyll/update/2022/02/28/encounter-at-the-goorlicker.html&quot;&gt;most recent water testing&lt;/a&gt; and was ready to fight; however, the
full extent of Brain Jones’ power is still unknown. Shroops the Almighty was especially furious because he was about to land a hit on King Louie. Nevertheless,
he didn’t want to get mixed up in something against the HBA, so he took the side of Sheeple Donnell. Shroops dashed towards Brian Jones and unleashed a punch
that could have sent a mountain flying to the moon. However, Brian Jones strengthened his skin by increasing the force of the molecular bonds of his
epidermial cells. He also increased his mass, so even if Shroops applied a large force (which he did), he would not accelerate. Momentum had to be
conserved, so a huge gust of wind blew towards the audience on the recieving side of the ring. The audience were getting worried about what was about to unfold,
so they began packing their bags and exiting the arena. I of course had to stay and witness history, but I found shelter behind the chairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brian Jones had expert control over physics, he would be a formidable foe. King Louie decided to help out Shroops, because defeating the foe would allow the
two to resume their boxing match. King Louie’s indomitable posture was unable to unnerve Brian Jones. Louie threw a hefty punch from the opposite corner of
the ring but Brian Jones set up a magnetic field, and due to the metal content in Louie’s blood, the punch was deflected. Truly, things were looking helpless
for the bunch. Brian Jones wasn’t even trying, he was just messing around. One man had power much greater than Shroops the Almighty, King Louie, and Sheeple
Donalvain himself! It was rigged, unfair, but Brian Jones was only getting started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank goodness he didn’t try causing Uranium to decay, he certainly could have. What Brian Jones did, however, was stop time. By speeding up beyond the
speed of light, Brian Jones was able to stop time. Somehow, I wasn’t affected, just like in the Daredevil Jack incident. Brain Jones was breaking the rules
of the universe. The speed of light was supposed to be the maximum speed in any condition, but Brain Jones exceeded all limits. He casually walked towards
Sheeple Duonnelll, and then noticed I wasn’t frozen. Without saying a word, the man began summoning more lightning. I had no escape, and I couldn’t get
grounded. I thought I would have to use the super-secret-emergency-only-use-in-a-catastrophic-moment HBA special device number 23, serial number 4022,
but my luck prevented the need of the super-secret-emergency-only-use-in-a-catastrophic-moment HBA special device number 23, serial number 4022. A portal of
light opened up, and out from it emerged ADALBERT BULSTRODE. THE KING HAD RETURNED!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Adalbert Bulstrode increased the dielectric
constant of the air so lightning wouldn’t form with Brian Jones’ voltage. “It’s been a while,” said Bulstrode. Ooh, and would you look at the time. It’s
time for me to resume ‘productive’ work. This has been Mister Mjir, popping in and now popping out.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>mister_mjir</name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><category term="News" /><category term="Sports" /><category term="Science" /><summary type="html">Hey guys, it’s been a while. I’m still afflicted by the procrastinatovirus. Doctors have been saying its incurable. Anyways, that’s a story for another time. If you don’t know about this February 31st stuff, be sure to check out part 1.</summary></entry></feed>